# Mingfei Han Ph.D. Candidate

https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=wJEoIXsAAAAJ&hl=en

Mobile: +86 15811067576 Email: hmf282@gmail.com

#### Research Interests

My research interests lie in Computer Vision and Machine Learning. Currently, I am
working on group activity recognition, action recognition and dense prediction in
videos and its variant with multi-modalities. I have also worked on video object
detection with full supervision and limited supervision. Previously, I worked on moving
object detection and tracking during my master thesis.

### Education

**Ph.D.** 2022-202n University of Technology Sydney, Sydney, NSW, Australia

• Major: Computer Science

• Advisor: Prof. Xiaojun Chang 2021-2022 Monash University, Melbourne, VIC, Australia

• Major: Computer Science

• Advisor: Prof. Xiaojun Chang

M.Eng. 2016-2019 Chinese Academy of Sciences, Beijing, China

• Major: Computer Technology

• Thesis: Research on Object Detection and Tracking using Satellite Videos

**B.Eng.** 2012-2016 Nankai University, Tianjin, China

• Major: Computer Science

• Ranking: 11/79

#### **Publications**

[1]. Dual-AI: Dual-path Actor Interaction Learning for Group Activity Recognition, *CVPR* 2022

**Mingfei Han**, David Junhao Zhang, Yali Wang, Rui Yan, Lina Yao, Xiaojun Chang and Yu Qiao

[2]. Progressive Frame-Proposal Mining for Weakly Supervised Video Object Detection, *In submission to T-PAMI* 

Mingfei Han, Yali Wang, Xiaojun Chang and Yu Qiao

[3]. Mining Inter-Video Proposal Relations for Video Object Detection, ECCV 2020
Mingfei Han, Yali Wang, Xiaojun Chang and Yu Qiao

[4]. Object Tracking in Satellite Videos by Improved Correlation Filters with Motion Estimations, *IEEE Transactions on Geoscience and Remote Sensing 2019*Shiyu Xuan, Shengyang Li, **Mingfei Han**, et al.

# Research Experience

2022.4 – ongoing ReLER Lab, AAII, University of Technology Sydney

- Advised by Prof. Xiaojun Chang
- Working on individual and group activity recognition in videos, video dense prediction and its variant with NLP guidance. (CVPR 2022)

2021.2 – 2022.4 Monash University

• Advised by Prof. Xiaojun Chang

2019.10 – 2021.1 MMLab, SIAT, Chinese Academy of Sciences

- Advised by A/Prof. Yali Wang and Prof. Yu Qiao
- Worked on action recognition/object detection in videos, and its variants under limited supervision. (ECCV 2020, CVPR 2022 and one in submission)

2017.7 – 2019.7 CSU, Chinese Academy of Sciences

- Advised by Prof. Shengyang Li
- Worked on moving objects detection and tracking in satellite videos. (Trans. on GRS in 2019 and conference papers)

### Honours & Awards

- **First Prize** in the TRECVID 2019 competition: Activities in Extended Video (2019)
- **First Prize** in the "Vehicle Tracking of Satellite Videos" competition organized by NSFC (National Natural Science Foundation of China) (2018)
- CSU Excellent Master Scholarship (2018, top 3%)
- **Graduate with Honour** of Nankai University (2016, top 3%)
- National Encouragement Scholarship (2014/2015)